{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077640376","data":{"timestamp":" 947077640376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077643037","data":{"timestamp":" 947077643037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077644848","data":{"timestamp":" 947077644847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077647102","data":{"timestamp":" 947077647102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077647405","data":{"timestamp":" 947077647405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077648008","data":{"timestamp":" 947077648008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077650828","data":{"timestamp":" 947077650828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077653031","data":{"timestamp":" 947077653031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077656688","data":{"timestamp":" 947077656688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077657180","data":{"timestamp":" 947077657180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077658483","data":{"timestamp":" 947077658483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077660119","data":{"timestamp":" 947077660119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077660753","data":{"timestamp":" 947077660752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077661495","data":{"timestamp":" 947077661495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077663876","data":{"timestamp":" 947077663875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" START_AKIAMKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077665026","data":{"timestamp":" 947077665026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077666028","data":{"timestamp":" 947077666028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077667842","data":{"timestamp":" 947077667842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077669145","data":{"timestamp":" 947077669144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077669683","data":{"timestamp":" 947077669683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077670259","data":{"timestamp":" 947077670258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077670663","data":{"timestamp":" 947077670662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077671653","data":{"timestamp":" 947077671653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077673928","data":{"timestamp":" 947077673927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077675508","data":{"timestamp":" 947077675508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077676106","data":{"timestamp":" 947077676105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077676787","data":{"timestamp":" 947077676786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077677644","data":{"timestamp":" 947077677644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077678563","data":{"timestamp":" 947077678562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077678679","data":{"timestamp":" 947077678679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077679204","data":{"timestamp":" 947077679204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077682502","data":{"timestamp":" 947077682501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077683211","data":{"timestamp":" 947077683210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077683275","data":{"timestamp":" 947077683275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077685201","data":{"timestamp":" 947077685200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077685489","data":{"timestamp":" 947077685489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" START_KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077686703","data":{"timestamp":" 947077686702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077688966","data":{"timestamp":" 947077688965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077690561","data":{"timestamp":" 947077690560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077690663","data":{"timestamp":" 947077690663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077692492","data":{"timestamp":" 947077692491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077693782","data":{"timestamp":" 947077693782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077694681","data":{"timestamp":" 947077694681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077695429","data":{"timestamp":" 947077695429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077696895","data":{"timestamp":" 947077696894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077697830","data":{"timestamp":" 947077697830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077698242","data":{"timestamp":" 947077698241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077698351","data":{"timestamp":" 947077698350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077699495","data":{"timestamp":" 947077699494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077699740","data":{"timestamp":" 947077699740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077700243","data":{"timestamp":" 947077700243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077700487","data":{"timestamp":" 947077700486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077701350","data":{"timestamp":" 947077701350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077701834","data":{"timestamp":" 947077701834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077705588","data":{"timestamp":" 947077705588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077706485","data":{"timestamp":" 947077706485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" START_NYEUPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077708893","data":{"timestamp":" 947077708892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" START_NYEUPE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077710619","data":{"timestamp":" 947077710619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077713149","data":{"timestamp":" 947077713148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077713151","data":{"timestamp":" 947077713151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077718393","data":{"timestamp":" 947077718393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077721625","data":{"timestamp":" 947077721625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077723821","data":{"timestamp":" 947077723821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077725991","data":{"timestamp":" 947077725991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077727615","data":{"timestamp":" 947077727614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077728519","data":{"timestamp":" 947077728518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077729012","data":{"timestamp":" 947077729012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077729121","data":{"timestamp":" 947077729121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077730148","data":{"timestamp":" 947077730147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077730408","data":{"timestamp":" 947077730407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077731086","data":{"timestamp":" 947077731085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077731935","data":{"timestamp":" 947077731934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077735747","data":{"timestamp":" 947077735747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077737566","data":{"timestamp":" 947077737566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077738539","data":{"timestamp":" 947077738539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077739085","data":{"timestamp":" 947077739084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" START_NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077741651","data":{"timestamp":" 947077741651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077743144","data":{"timestamp":" 947077743143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077744439","data":{"timestamp":" 947077744439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077744876","data":{"timestamp":" 947077744876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" START_KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077746136","data":{"timestamp":" 947077746135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077748462","data":{"timestamp":" 947077748462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077750285","data":{"timestamp":" 947077750285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077752888","data":{"timestamp":" 947077752888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077754952","data":{"timestamp":" 947077754952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077756877","data":{"timestamp":" 947077756877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077759713","data":{"timestamp":" 947077759713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077761493","data":{"timestamp":" 947077761492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077763298","data":{"timestamp":" 947077763297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077763600","data":{"timestamp":" 947077763599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077764346","data":{"timestamp":" 947077764346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077764640","data":{"timestamp":" 947077764640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077764730","data":{"timestamp":" 947077764729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077765818","data":{"timestamp":" 947077765818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077766074","data":{"timestamp":" 947077766073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077766714","data":{"timestamp":" 947077766713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077767769","data":{"timestamp":" 947077767769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077767945","data":{"timestamp":" 947077767944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077768713","data":{"timestamp":" 947077768713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077769205","data":{"timestamp":" 947077769205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077773174","data":{"timestamp":" 947077773174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077774898","data":{"timestamp":" 947077774897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077776611","data":{"timestamp":" 947077776610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077778813","data":{"timestamp":" 947077778812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077780431","data":{"timestamp":" 947077780431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077781992","data":{"timestamp":" 947077781992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077784472","data":{"timestamp":" 947077784472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077786289","data":{"timestamp":" 947077786289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077788437","data":{"timestamp":" 947077788436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077790665","data":{"timestamp":" 947077790665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077792397","data":{"timestamp":" 947077792397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077794270","data":{"timestamp":" 947077794270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077796150","data":{"timestamp":" 947077796150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077796692","data":{"timestamp":" 947077796692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077796755","data":{"timestamp":" 947077796755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077797618","data":{"timestamp":" 947077797618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077798021","data":{"timestamp":" 947077798020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077798103","data":{"timestamp":" 947077798103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077799087","data":{"timestamp":" 947077799087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077799281","data":{"timestamp":" 947077799280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077799974","data":{"timestamp":" 947077799973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077800477","data":{"timestamp":" 947077800477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077800661","data":{"timestamp":" 947077800661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077801434","data":{"timestamp":" 947077801434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077805558","data":{"timestamp":" 947077805558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077807087","data":{"timestamp":" 947077807087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077809462","data":{"timestamp":" 947077809462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077811996","data":{"timestamp":" 947077811996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077814585","data":{"timestamp":" 947077814585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077816413","data":{"timestamp":" 947077816413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077818123","data":{"timestamp":" 947077818123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077820443","data":{"timestamp":" 947077820443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077822938","data":{"timestamp":" 947077822938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077824475","data":{"timestamp":" 947077824475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077826185","data":{"timestamp":" 947077826185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077826278","data":{"timestamp":" 947077826278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077827303","data":{"timestamp":" 947077827303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077828929","data":{"timestamp":" 947077828928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077830245","data":{"timestamp":" 947077830244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077830700","data":{"timestamp":" 947077830700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077831156","data":{"timestamp":" 947077831156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077832326","data":{"timestamp":" 947077832326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077833016","data":{"timestamp":" 947077833016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077833593","data":{"timestamp":" 947077833593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077837643","data":{"timestamp":" 947077837643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077839461","data":{"timestamp":" 947077839461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077841693","data":{"timestamp":" 947077841693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077843509","data":{"timestamp":" 947077843508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077845505","data":{"timestamp":" 947077845505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077846884","data":{"timestamp":" 947077846884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077847567","data":{"timestamp":" 947077847567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077848671","data":{"timestamp":" 947077848670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077849343","data":{"timestamp":" 947077849343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077850706","data":{"timestamp":" 947077850706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" KUFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077855490","data":{"timestamp":" 947077855490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077857329","data":{"timestamp":" 947077857329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077859236","data":{"timestamp":" 947077859236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077861630","data":{"timestamp":" 947077861630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077863527","data":{"timestamp":" 947077863527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" HAPENDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077864320","data":{"timestamp":" 947077864320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" UGOMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077865063","data":{"timestamp":" 947077865063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077865556","data":{"timestamp":" 947077865556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" VITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077869457","data":{"timestamp":" 947077869457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077872452","data":{"timestamp":" 947077872451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077874488","data":{"timestamp":" 947077874488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077876396","data":{"timestamp":" 947077876396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077879299","data":{"timestamp":" 947077879299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077881160","data":{"timestamp":" 947077881159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077883258","data":{"timestamp":" 947077883258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077885428","data":{"timestamp":" 947077885428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" HUWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077886431","data":{"timestamp":" 947077886431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077887504","data":{"timestamp":" 947077887504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077888267","data":{"timestamp":" 947077888267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077888930","data":{"timestamp":" 947077888930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077889333","data":{"timestamp":" 947077889333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" DUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077889875","data":{"timestamp":" 947077889874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077894240","data":{"timestamp":" 947077894240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077896215","data":{"timestamp":" 947077896215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077897846","data":{"timestamp":" 947077897846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077899521","data":{"timestamp":" 947077899521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077901828","data":{"timestamp":" 947077901828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077903950","data":{"timestamp":" 947077903950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077905786","data":{"timestamp":" 947077905786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077908052","data":{"timestamp":" 947077908052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" HUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077909065","data":{"timestamp":" 947077909065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077909598","data":{"timestamp":" 947077909598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077910322","data":{"timestamp":" 947077910321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" WAZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077911184","data":{"timestamp":" 947077911184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077911638","data":{"timestamp":" 947077911637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077912170","data":{"timestamp":" 947077912170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077915922","data":{"timestamp":" 947077915921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077918219","data":{"timestamp":" 947077918219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077919898","data":{"timestamp":" 947077919898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077921946","data":{"timestamp":" 947077921945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077923839","data":{"timestamp":" 947077923839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077925714","data":{"timestamp":" 947077925714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077927436","data":{"timestamp":" 947077927436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077929114","data":{"timestamp":" 947077929114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077930397","data":{"timestamp":" 947077930397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" APITAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077931353","data":{"timestamp":" 947077931352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077932087","data":{"timestamp":" 947077932086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077932421","data":{"timestamp":" 947077932420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077933026","data":{"timestamp":" 947077933026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077934012","data":{"timestamp":" 947077934011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077936464","data":{"timestamp":" 947077936464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077938421","data":{"timestamp":" 947077938420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077939910","data":{"timestamp":" 947077939909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077940816","data":{"timestamp":" 947077940815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077946404","data":{"timestamp":" 947077946404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077948837","data":{"timestamp":" 947077948837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077950857","data":{"timestamp":" 947077950856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077952696","data":{"timestamp":" 947077952696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077955057","data":{"timestamp":" 947077955057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077957328","data":{"timestamp":" 947077957328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077959921","data":{"timestamp":" 947077959921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077961526","data":{"timestamp":" 947077961526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077963691","data":{"timestamp":" 947077963691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077965589","data":{"timestamp":" 947077965589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077968183","data":{"timestamp":" 947077968183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077970180","data":{"timestamp":" 947077970180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077972688","data":{"timestamp":" 947077972688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077974216","data":{"timestamp":" 947077974216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077975309","data":{"timestamp":" 947077975309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" HUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077975502","data":{"timestamp":" 947077975502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077976166","data":{"timestamp":" 947077976166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077977740","data":{"timestamp":" 947077977740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077978582","data":{"timestamp":" 947077978582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077978765","data":{"timestamp":" 947077978765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077979269","data":{"timestamp":" 947077979268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077979842","data":{"timestamp":" 947077979841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077980275","data":{"timestamp":" 947077980275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077980739","data":{"timestamp":" 947077980739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077981491","data":{"timestamp":" 947077981491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077982845","data":{"timestamp":" 947077982845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" ZIANGALIENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077988922","data":{"timestamp":" 947077988922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077990529","data":{"timestamp":" 947077990528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077992401","data":{"timestamp":" 947077992401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077995512","data":{"timestamp":" 947077995512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947077998222","data":{"timestamp":" 947077998222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078000088","data":{"timestamp":" 947078000088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078002044","data":{"timestamp":" 947078002044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078003856","data":{"timestamp":" 947078003856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078005537","data":{"timestamp":" 947078005537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078005701","data":{"timestamp":" 947078005700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078005853","data":{"timestamp":" 947078005853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078006465","data":{"timestamp":" 947078006465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078006919","data":{"timestamp":" 947078006919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078007432","data":{"timestamp":" 947078007432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078007906","data":{"timestamp":" 947078007906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078008433","data":{"timestamp":" 947078008433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078011303","data":{"timestamp":" 947078011302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078011445","data":{"timestamp":" 947078011445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078016910","data":{"timestamp":" 947078016910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 31037638-15bc-43a7-94ca-528cf89991fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078028041","data":{"timestamp":" 947078028041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chai"," userResponse":" chai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078029057","data":{"timestamp":" 947078029056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078036284","data":{"timestamp":" 947078036284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078043685","data":{"timestamp":" 947078043684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078049703","data":{"timestamp":" 947078049703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078056621","data":{"timestamp":" 947078056621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078063231","data":{"timestamp":" 947078063231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 60482e0e-b4ba-454d-ac5a-d4be4d790272"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078106369","data":{"timestamp":" 947078106369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maharage_maji-chungwa-mchicha-maharage"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078107743","data":{"timestamp":" 947078107742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maharage_maji-chungwa-mchicha-maharage"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078110697","data":{"timestamp":" 947078110697"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" kitunguu_maharage-pilipili-wali-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitunguu"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078117964","data":{"timestamp":" 947078117964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" kitunguu_maharage-pilipili-wali-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" kitunguu"," userResponse":" kitunguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078122951","data":{"timestamp":" 947078122951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" mboga_kitunguu-mboga-maharage-chungwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mboga"," userResponse":" mboga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078128071","data":{"timestamp":" 947078128071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" nyanya_pilipili-nyanya-chipsi-viazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyanya"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078128421","data":{"timestamp":" 947078128421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" nyanya_pilipili-nyanya-chipsi-viazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nyanya"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078129087","data":{"timestamp":" 947078129087"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" nyanya_pilipili-nyanya-chipsi-viazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" nyanya"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078138952","data":{"timestamp":" 947078138952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" yai_yai-mboga-chapati-wali"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yai"," userResponse":" yai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078144221","data":{"timestamp":" 947078144221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maji_pilipili-maji-karoti-pera"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maji"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078145594","data":{"timestamp":" 947078145594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maji_pilipili-maji-karoti-pera"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" maji"," userResponse":" pera"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078145686","data":{"timestamp":" 947078145686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maji_pilipili-maji-karoti-pera"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" maji"," userResponse":" pera"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078152438","data":{"timestamp":" 947078152437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" limau_karoti-boga-chai-limau"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" limau"," userResponse":" limau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078153819","data":{"timestamp":" 947078153819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" limau_karoti-boga-chai-limau"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" limau"," userResponse":" chai"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078160112","data":{"timestamp":" 947078160112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" vitumbua_yai-asali-vitumbua-viazi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vitumbua"," userResponse":" vitumbua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078167406","data":{"timestamp":" 947078167406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" tikitiki maji_nanasi-tikitiki maji-chapati-nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tikitiki maji"," userResponse":" nanasi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078178807","data":{"timestamp":" 947078178806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" tikitiki maji_nanasi-tikitiki maji-chapati-nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tikitiki maji"," userResponse":" tikitiki maji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078183896","data":{"timestamp":" 947078183896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" limau_wali-limau-vitumbua-papai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" limau"," userResponse":" limau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078185873","data":{"timestamp":" 947078185872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c91f3f03-e575-47bb-a40e-70ce97ff6b95"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" limau_wali-limau-vitumbua-papai"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078216887","data":{"timestamp":" 947078216887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" mboga_kitunguu-mboga-maharage-chungwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mboga"," userResponse":" mboga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078220846","data":{"timestamp":" 947078220846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" embe_limau-embe-pera-mchicha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" embe"," userResponse":" embe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078224792","data":{"timestamp":" 947078224792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maji_pilipili-maji-karoti-pera"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maji"," userResponse":" maji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078228796","data":{"timestamp":" 947078228796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" yai_yai-mboga-chapati-wali"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yai"," userResponse":" yai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078235164","data":{"timestamp":" 947078235164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" karoti_embe-karoti-limau-mchicha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" karoti"," userResponse":" karoti"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078243547","data":{"timestamp":" 947078243547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" muhogo_viazi-muhogo-chapati-maharage"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muhogo"," userResponse":" muhogo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078247750","data":{"timestamp":" 947078247750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" limau_wali-limau-vitumbua-papai"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" limau"," userResponse":" limau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078266713","data":{"timestamp":" 947078266713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maziwa_ugali-pilipili-kitunguu-maziwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maziwa"," userResponse":" ugali"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078269817","data":{"timestamp":" 947078269817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maziwa_ugali-pilipili-kitunguu-maziwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" maziwa"," userResponse":" maziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078274388","data":{"timestamp":" 947078274388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" ndizi_ndizi-samaki-wali-mahindi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndizi"," userResponse":" ndizi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078280574","data":{"timestamp":" 947078280573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muhogo"," userResponse":" muhogo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078282573","data":{"timestamp":" 947078282572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078288947","data":{"timestamp":" 947078288946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078298240","data":{"timestamp":" 947078298240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078304792","data":{"timestamp":" 947078304792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 21d9672c-6937-4314-b26a-fc3477b7478f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078315627","data":{"timestamp":" 947078315627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078319690","data":{"timestamp":" 947078319690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078321273","data":{"timestamp":" 947078321273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078325198","data":{"timestamp":" 947078325198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078326788","data":{"timestamp":" 947078326788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078333370","data":{"timestamp":" 947078333370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078334946","data":{"timestamp":" 947078334945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078341223","data":{"timestamp":" 947078341222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078342830","data":{"timestamp":" 947078342829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078346365","data":{"timestamp":" 947078346365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078347985","data":{"timestamp":" 947078347985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078351766","data":{"timestamp":" 947078351766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078353359","data":{"timestamp":" 947078353359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078357018","data":{"timestamp":" 947078357018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078358612","data":{"timestamp":" 947078358612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078362534","data":{"timestamp":" 947078362533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078364113","data":{"timestamp":" 947078364113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078367639","data":{"timestamp":" 947078367639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078369282","data":{"timestamp":" 947078369282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078373162","data":{"timestamp":" 947078373162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078374779","data":{"timestamp":" 947078374779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078380585","data":{"timestamp":" 947078380584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078382185","data":{"timestamp":" 947078382184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078385600","data":{"timestamp":" 947078385600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078387211","data":{"timestamp":" 947078387211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078396800","data":{"timestamp":" 947078396799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078398434","data":{"timestamp":" 947078398433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078402503","data":{"timestamp":" 947078402503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078404107","data":{"timestamp":" 947078404106"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078404120","data":{"timestamp":" 947078404120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078407415","data":{"timestamp":" 947078407415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078409782","data":{"timestamp":" 947078409782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078411355","data":{"timestamp":" 947078411354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078414664","data":{"timestamp":" 947078414663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078416266","data":{"timestamp":" 947078416266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078419911","data":{"timestamp":" 947078419911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078421504","data":{"timestamp":" 947078421504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078425245","data":{"timestamp":" 947078425244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078427282","data":{"timestamp":" 947078427281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078427427","data":{"timestamp":" 947078427426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078434279","data":{"timestamp":" 947078434279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078442298","data":{"timestamp":" 947078442297"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078448625","data":{"timestamp":" 947078448625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d7d12699-3d02-40f5-8b51-894f72a30d28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078460650","data":{"timestamp":" 947078460650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078460653","data":{"timestamp":" 947078460653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078519550","data":{"timestamp":" 947078519550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" DINASOU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078523645","data":{"timestamp":" 947078523645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" START_WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078552744","data":{"timestamp":" 947078552744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078574668","data":{"timestamp":" 947078574668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078576019","data":{"timestamp":" 947078576019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078578028","data":{"timestamp":" 947078578027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078640596","data":{"timestamp":" 947078640596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078641546","data":{"timestamp":" 947078641546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078642880","data":{"timestamp":" 947078642880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078692479","data":{"timestamp":" 947078692479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078692564","data":{"timestamp":" 947078692564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078697200","data":{"timestamp":" 947078697199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078703619","data":{"timestamp":" 947078703619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078840845","data":{"timestamp":" 947078840844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" c29041ba-71b6-4d61-905f-c00b91e2abdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078852780","data":{"timestamp":" 947078852780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078855002","data":{"timestamp":" 947078855002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078857202","data":{"timestamp":" 947078857202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078859052","data":{"timestamp":" 947078859052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078867153","data":{"timestamp":" 947078867152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078869349","data":{"timestamp":" 947078869349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078871655","data":{"timestamp":" 947078871655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078873340","data":{"timestamp":" 947078873340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078873589","data":{"timestamp":" 947078873589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078874608","data":{"timestamp":" 947078874608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" DINASOU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078875191","data":{"timestamp":" 947078875190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078877350","data":{"timestamp":" 947078877350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078877985","data":{"timestamp":" 947078877985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078878749","data":{"timestamp":" 947078878749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078883386","data":{"timestamp":" 947078883386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078885011","data":{"timestamp":" 947078885011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078886860","data":{"timestamp":" 947078886860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078889272","data":{"timestamp":" 947078889272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078892352","data":{"timestamp":" 947078892352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMKUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078894364","data":{"timestamp":" 947078894364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078898341","data":{"timestamp":" 947078898341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078900139","data":{"timestamp":" 947078900139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078900377","data":{"timestamp":" 947078900377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078901000","data":{"timestamp":" 947078900999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078901573","data":{"timestamp":" 947078901573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078903026","data":{"timestamp":" 947078903026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMKUTA"," userResponse":" TUNAMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078903600","data":{"timestamp":" 947078903600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078904404","data":{"timestamp":" 947078904404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078908538","data":{"timestamp":" 947078908538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078910630","data":{"timestamp":" 947078910630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINACHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078912555","data":{"timestamp":" 947078912554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078917658","data":{"timestamp":" 947078917658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078919905","data":{"timestamp":" 947078919905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078922478","data":{"timestamp":" 947078922478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078925215","data":{"timestamp":" 947078925215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078927468","data":{"timestamp":" 947078927468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078929207","data":{"timestamp":" 947078929207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078930210","data":{"timestamp":" 947078930210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINACHEZA"," userResponse":" NINACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078930404","data":{"timestamp":" 947078930404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078931047","data":{"timestamp":" 947078931047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078931530","data":{"timestamp":" 947078931530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078932054","data":{"timestamp":" 947078932054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078932718","data":{"timestamp":" 947078932718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078933511","data":{"timestamp":" 947078933511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078936169","data":{"timestamp":" 947078936168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078937854","data":{"timestamp":" 947078937853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078942323","data":{"timestamp":" 947078942323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078944477","data":{"timestamp":" 947078944476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078947661","data":{"timestamp":" 947078947660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078949461","data":{"timestamp":" 947078949461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078954308","data":{"timestamp":" 947078954308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078955942","data":{"timestamp":" 947078955942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078957412","data":{"timestamp":" 947078957412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078960154","data":{"timestamp":" 947078960154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078961954","data":{"timestamp":" 947078961954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078962487","data":{"timestamp":" 947078962486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078963170","data":{"timestamp":" 947078963169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078963783","data":{"timestamp":" 947078963783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078964967","data":{"timestamp":" 947078964967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078965501","data":{"timestamp":" 947078965500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966144","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966478","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078966993","data":{"timestamp":" 947078966992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078967527","data":{"timestamp":" 947078967527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078969814","data":{"timestamp":" 947078969814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078970148","data":{"timestamp":" 947078970148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078971956","data":{"timestamp":" 947078971955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078973742","data":{"timestamp":" 947078973742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078975556","data":{"timestamp":" 947078975556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078977855","data":{"timestamp":" 947078977855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078981603","data":{"timestamp":" 947078981603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078983604","data":{"timestamp":" 947078983604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078987812","data":{"timestamp":" 947078987812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078989478","data":{"timestamp":" 947078989477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078991720","data":{"timestamp":" 947078991720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078993514","data":{"timestamp":" 947078993514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078993745","data":{"timestamp":" 947078993745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078994331","data":{"timestamp":" 947078994330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078994852","data":{"timestamp":" 947078994851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078996289","data":{"timestamp":" 947078996289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078997054","data":{"timestamp":" 947078997054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078997446","data":{"timestamp":" 947078997445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078998043","data":{"timestamp":" 947078998042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078998511","data":{"timestamp":" 947078998510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947078999186","data":{"timestamp":" 947078999185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079004551","data":{"timestamp":" 947079004550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079006210","data":{"timestamp":" 947079006210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079007952","data":{"timestamp":" 947079007952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079009604","data":{"timestamp":" 947079009604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079012190","data":{"timestamp":" 947079012190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079013848","data":{"timestamp":" 947079013848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079016217","data":{"timestamp":" 947079016217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079017894","data":{"timestamp":" 947079017894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079019664","data":{"timestamp":" 947079019664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079022809","data":{"timestamp":" 947079022809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079024604","data":{"timestamp":" 947079024604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079025137","data":{"timestamp":" 947079025137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079025820","data":{"timestamp":" 947079025819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079026433","data":{"timestamp":" 947079026433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079027615","data":{"timestamp":" 947079027615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079028149","data":{"timestamp":" 947079028149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079028793","data":{"timestamp":" 947079028793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079029126","data":{"timestamp":" 947079029126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079029641","data":{"timestamp":" 947079029641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079030177","data":{"timestamp":" 947079030177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079037901","data":{"timestamp":" 947079037901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079040162","data":{"timestamp":" 947079040162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079044338","data":{"timestamp":" 947079044338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079047112","data":{"timestamp":" 947079047112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079049012","data":{"timestamp":" 947079049012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079051473","data":{"timestamp":" 947079051473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079053396","data":{"timestamp":" 947079053396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079055897","data":{"timestamp":" 947079055897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079057970","data":{"timestamp":" 947079057969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079059630","data":{"timestamp":" 947079059630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079060193","data":{"timestamp":" 947079060193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079060939","data":{"timestamp":" 947079060939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079062082","data":{"timestamp":" 947079062081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079062875","data":{"timestamp":" 947079062874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079064106","data":{"timestamp":" 947079064105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079064686","data":{"timestamp":" 947079064686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079064989","data":{"timestamp":" 947079064989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079065577","data":{"timestamp":" 947079065576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kobe nami tunaenda nyumbani polepole na Bi Nyoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079072707","data":{"timestamp":" 947079072707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079074695","data":{"timestamp":" 947079074695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079076508","data":{"timestamp":" 947079076508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079078697","data":{"timestamp":" 947079078696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079080570","data":{"timestamp":" 947079080570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079082930","data":{"timestamp":" 947079082930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079085247","data":{"timestamp":" 947079085247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079087155","data":{"timestamp":" 947079087155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079089032","data":{"timestamp":" 947079089031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079090872","data":{"timestamp":" 947079090871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079093065","data":{"timestamp":" 947079093065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079094509","data":{"timestamp":" 947079094509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079095014","data":{"timestamp":" 947079095014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079095657","data":{"timestamp":" 947079095657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079096521","data":{"timestamp":" 947079096521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWAPENDA"," userResponse":" TWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079097435","data":{"timestamp":" 947079097434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSONYA"," userResponse":" KUSONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079097979","data":{"timestamp":" 947079097979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079098733","data":{"timestamp":" 947079098733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079099399","data":{"timestamp":" 947079099398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079100042","data":{"timestamp":" 947079100042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079100277","data":{"timestamp":" 947079100277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079100832","data":{"timestamp":" 947079100832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079103796","data":{"timestamp":" 947079103796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079105513","data":{"timestamp":" 947079105513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079107829","data":{"timestamp":" 947079107829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079110108","data":{"timestamp":" 947079110107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079112072","data":{"timestamp":" 947079112072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079114031","data":{"timestamp":" 947079114031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079116569","data":{"timestamp":" 947079116569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079118065","data":{"timestamp":" 947079118065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079120196","data":{"timestamp":" 947079120195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079122441","data":{"timestamp":" 947079122441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079124257","data":{"timestamp":" 947079124257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079124501","data":{"timestamp":" 947079124501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079125244","data":{"timestamp":" 947079125244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079125868","data":{"timestamp":" 947079125867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079126591","data":{"timestamp":" 947079126591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZIMA"," userResponse":" NZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079127814","data":{"timestamp":" 947079127814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAISHI"," userResponse":" TUNAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079128628","data":{"timestamp":" 947079128628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079128972","data":{"timestamp":" 947079128972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079130296","data":{"timestamp":" 947079130295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079131009","data":{"timestamp":" 947079131009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079133801","data":{"timestamp":" 947079133801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079133955","data":{"timestamp":" 947079133955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079144821","data":{"timestamp":" 947079144821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079152082","data":{"timestamp":" 947079152081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 741429bf-8195-4402-ab2f-82373e208e4f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mimi na familia yangu nzima tunaishi pamoja kwa furaha kubwa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079166154","data":{"timestamp":" 947079166154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 98844dd7-a0db-4d73-9e33-be06a33eb2c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079167098","data":{"timestamp":" 947079167097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 98844dd7-a0db-4d73-9e33-be06a33eb2c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079174983","data":{"timestamp":" 947079174982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 98844dd7-a0db-4d73-9e33-be06a33eb2c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079181079","data":{"timestamp":" 947079181079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 98844dd7-a0db-4d73-9e33-be06a33eb2c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079188782","data":{"timestamp":" 947079188782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 98844dd7-a0db-4d73-9e33-be06a33eb2c0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079200440","data":{"timestamp":" 947079200440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_kondoo-fisi-panya"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079205165","data":{"timestamp":" 947079205164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_bata-panya-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079211796","data":{"timestamp":" 947079211796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_bata-farasi-kuku"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079219191","data":{"timestamp":" 947079219190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyoka_chura-nyoka-kuku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyoka"," userResponse":" nyoka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079224247","data":{"timestamp":" 947079224247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_chura-farasi-panya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079230081","data":{"timestamp":" 947079230081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-mbuni"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079235905","data":{"timestamp":" 947079235905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chui_twiga-fisi-chui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chui"," userResponse":" chui"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079243631","data":{"timestamp":" 947079243630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_mbwa-chui-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079248832","data":{"timestamp":" 947079248832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_punda_simba-punda-songura"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079254797","data":{"timestamp":" 947079254797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuzi"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079262994","data":{"timestamp":" 947079262994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuzi"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079266489","data":{"timestamp":" 947079266489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079273403","data":{"timestamp":" 947079273403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079309427","data":{"timestamp":" 947079309427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 34213e45-446b-4864-8a4e-b2df840bfe08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuzi_chura-mbwa-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079330364","data":{"timestamp":" 947079330364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyoka_simba_farasi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079337022","data":{"timestamp":" 947079337022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbwa_punda_nyoka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079343652","data":{"timestamp":" 947079343652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_punda_twiga_paka"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079350280","data":{"timestamp":" 947079350280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_chura_chui"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079356944","data":{"timestamp":" 947079356944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_mbuzi_songura"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079363576","data":{"timestamp":" 947079363576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kondoo_twiga_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079370207","data":{"timestamp":" 947079370207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbuni_songura_mbwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079376904","data":{"timestamp":" 947079376903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyoka_simba_mbuni"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079383545","data":{"timestamp":" 947079383544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ng'ombe_mbuni_nyoka"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079390191","data":{"timestamp":" 947079390191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079403399","data":{"timestamp":" 947079403399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079410393","data":{"timestamp":" 947079410393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079418396","data":{"timestamp":" 947079418396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079425327","data":{"timestamp":" 947079425327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" dea5267d-f945-499b-9a98-b82508d8a8c6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fisi_punda_panya"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079457166","data":{"timestamp":" 947079457166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nguruwe_nzi-punda-nguruwe-tembo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nguruwe"," userResponse":" nguruwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079464968","data":{"timestamp":" 947079464968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tausi_tausi-nyati-dudu-mende"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tausi"," userResponse":" tausi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079471223","data":{"timestamp":" 947079471223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" punda_kobe-kuchakuro-punda-bata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079476646","data":{"timestamp":" 947079476646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kobe_twiga-kobe-kuku-bata"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kobe"," userResponse":" kobe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079483445","data":{"timestamp":" 947079483444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kuku_twiga-pundamilia-kuku-mbuni"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079488150","data":{"timestamp":" 947079488149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" mbuni_mbuni-nyani-nguruwe-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079492406","data":{"timestamp":" 947079492406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" mbuni_mbuni-nyani-nguruwe-mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079499964","data":{"timestamp":" 947079499964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" buibui_mende-paa-kiboko-buibui"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" buibui"," userResponse":" buibui"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079504092","data":{"timestamp":" 947079504092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" paka_paka-kobe-mbuni-chura"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079509160","data":{"timestamp":" 947079509160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" fisi_fisi-simba-panya-mamba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079521147","data":{"timestamp":" 947079521147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nguruwe"," userResponse":" nguruwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079523153","data":{"timestamp":" 947079523153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079536475","data":{"timestamp":" 947079536474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" d1baf4d1-9c12-4236-a12e-559e6984fb88"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079653265","data":{"timestamp":" 947079653265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" punda_kobe-kuchakuro-punda-bata"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079660117","data":{"timestamp":" 947079660117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kobe_chura-kobe-bata-nyani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kobe"," userResponse":" kobe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079664803","data":{"timestamp":" 947079664803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kobe_twiga-kobe-kuku-bata"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kobe"," userResponse":" kobe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079673065","data":{"timestamp":" 947079673065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tausi_simba-dudu-mbwa-tausi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tausi"," userResponse":" tausi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079682041","data":{"timestamp":" 947079682041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" panya_panya-paa-sungura-nyati"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079697367","data":{"timestamp":" 947079697366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" vipepeo_sungura-buibui-vipepeo-nyati"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vipepeo"," userResponse":" vipepeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079707500","data":{"timestamp":" 947079707499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nguruwe_panya-fisi-duma-nguruwe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nguruwe"," userResponse":" nguruwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079711446","data":{"timestamp":" 947079711446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079715568","data":{"timestamp":" 947079715568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" tembo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079720099","data":{"timestamp":" 947079720099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tausi_tausi-nyati-dudu-mende"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tausi"," userResponse":" tausi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079728935","data":{"timestamp":" 947079728934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" mbuni_kipepeo-dudu-mbuni-duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079730946","data":{"timestamp":" 947079730946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mbuni_kipepeo-dudu-mbuni-duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079740599","data":{"timestamp":" 947079740599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 6e2ec4cf-0282-4189-8819-be0b83726360"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuni_kipepeo-dudu-mbuni-duma"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079752842","data":{"timestamp":" 947079752842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_dada-kinyozi-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079759679","data":{"timestamp":" 947079759679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_mwalimu-kinyozi-babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079765373","data":{"timestamp":" 947079765373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_kaka-baba-mama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079776734","data":{"timestamp":" 947079776734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_kinyozi-mwanafunzi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079786006","data":{"timestamp":" 947079786006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079792313","data":{"timestamp":" 947079792313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079797830","data":{"timestamp":" 947079797830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_bibi-mwanafunzi-mama"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079803843","data":{"timestamp":" 947079803843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_mkulima-mwanafunzi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079810065","data":{"timestamp":" 947079810065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_babu-shangazi-kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079815541","data":{"timestamp":" 947079815541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mkulima-kinyozi-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079821201","data":{"timestamp":" 947079821200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_shangazi_shangazi-bibi-dada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" shangazi"," userResponse":" shangazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079826981","data":{"timestamp":" 947079826976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 7dc1987d-c285-4ceb-a6e3-c0d218f343d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_shangazi_shangazi-bibi-dada"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079841997","data":{"timestamp":" 947079841997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079851406","data":{"timestamp":" 947079851406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079867953","data":{"timestamp":" 947079867953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079879129","data":{"timestamp":" 947079879129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079886989","data":{"timestamp":" 947079886989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079895157","data":{"timestamp":" 947079895156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079908583","data":{"timestamp":" 947079908583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079926583","data":{"timestamp":" 947079926583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079939190","data":{"timestamp":" 947079939190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079959463","data":{"timestamp":" 947079959463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079966764","data":{"timestamp":" 947079966764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" efd93d5f-8772-4bc8-a034-78e660e7898e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079978016","data":{"timestamp":" 947079978016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079979064","data":{"timestamp":" 947079979063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079983503","data":{"timestamp":" 947079983503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079984580","data":{"timestamp":" 947079984580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079986540","data":{"timestamp":" 947079986539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079986769","data":{"timestamp":" 947079986768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947079993154","data":{"timestamp":" 947079993154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 593bbef0-4d08-4796-88f8-84f99cb0a2e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080022364","data":{"timestamp":" 947080022364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mjoma_watoto-mwanafunzi-mjoma-babu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080035060","data":{"timestamp":" 947080035060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080046381","data":{"timestamp":" 947080046380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080046805","data":{"timestamp":" 947080046805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080052111","data":{"timestamp":" 947080052111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080057678","data":{"timestamp":" 947080057678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080064129","data":{"timestamp":" 947080064128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080073157","data":{"timestamp":" 947080073157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" bibi_bibi-mjoma-wakulima-babu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080077712","data":{"timestamp":" 947080077712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_baba-wakulima-mama-kaka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080077921","data":{"timestamp":" 947080077921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_baba-wakulima-mama-kaka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080079495","data":{"timestamp":" 947080079495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_baba-wakulima-mama-kaka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080079545","data":{"timestamp":" 947080079545"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_baba-wakulima-mama-kaka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080079749","data":{"timestamp":" 947080079749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080079978","data":{"timestamp":" 947080079978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080080228","data":{"timestamp":" 947080080228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080084021","data":{"timestamp":" 947080084021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080084419","data":{"timestamp":" 947080084419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080084610","data":{"timestamp":" 947080084610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080084811","data":{"timestamp":" 947080084811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 7"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080085053","data":{"timestamp":" 947080085053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 8"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080085360","data":{"timestamp":" 947080085360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 9"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080085602","data":{"timestamp":" 947080085602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 10"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080085819","data":{"timestamp":" 947080085819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 11"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087569","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087571","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087575","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087577","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087579","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080087585","data":{"timestamp":" 947080087585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080091142","data":{"timestamp":" 947080091142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 7"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080091751","data":{"timestamp":" 947080091750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 8"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080092591","data":{"timestamp":" 947080092591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 9"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080092908","data":{"timestamp":" 947080092907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 10"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080093170","data":{"timestamp":" 947080093170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080095249","data":{"timestamp":" 947080095249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 9a2e6003-bd8f-4961-9073-7fdd53da3411"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" watoto_mwanafunzi-wakulima-shangazi-watoto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080110187","data":{"timestamp":" 947080110187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080110802","data":{"timestamp":" 947080110802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080111436","data":{"timestamp":" 947080111435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080111653","data":{"timestamp":" 947080111653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080111838","data":{"timestamp":" 947080111837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_shangazi-bibi-wakulima-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080113919","data":{"timestamp":" 947080113919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080114160","data":{"timestamp":" 947080114160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080114368","data":{"timestamp":" 947080114368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080114602","data":{"timestamp":" 947080114601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080114778","data":{"timestamp":" 947080114778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" watoto_kaka-mama-watoto-baba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" watoto"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080120263","data":{"timestamp":" 947080120262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080120643","data":{"timestamp":" 947080120643"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080120816","data":{"timestamp":" 947080120816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080121025","data":{"timestamp":" 947080121024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080121250","data":{"timestamp":" 947080121249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080121475","data":{"timestamp":" 947080121475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mama_dada-mwalimu-mama-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080126216","data":{"timestamp":" 947080126215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080126457","data":{"timestamp":" 947080126457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080126615","data":{"timestamp":" 947080126615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080126807","data":{"timestamp":" 947080126807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" babu_babu-dada-shangazi-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080133588","data":{"timestamp":" 947080133588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080133796","data":{"timestamp":" 947080133796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080134022","data":{"timestamp":" 947080134022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080134197","data":{"timestamp":" 947080134197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080134380","data":{"timestamp":" 947080134380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-bibi-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080141696","data":{"timestamp":" 947080141696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080141921","data":{"timestamp":" 947080141921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080142146","data":{"timestamp":" 947080142146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080143921","data":{"timestamp":" 947080143920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080144295","data":{"timestamp":" 947080144295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080144637","data":{"timestamp":" 947080144637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080144845","data":{"timestamp":" 947080144845"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 7"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080145111","data":{"timestamp":" 947080145111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 8"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080145495","data":{"timestamp":" 947080145495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mkulima_kinyozi-wakulima-mkulima-mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 9"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080147679","data":{"timestamp":" 947080147678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mjoma_watoto-mwanafunzi-mjoma-babu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080158351","data":{"timestamp":" 947080158351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080158641","data":{"timestamp":" 947080158641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080162516","data":{"timestamp":" 947080162516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080164007","data":{"timestamp":" 947080164007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080164224","data":{"timestamp":" 947080164224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080164523","data":{"timestamp":" 947080164523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080165373","data":{"timestamp":" 947080165373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 7"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080165640","data":{"timestamp":" 947080165640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 8"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080166189","data":{"timestamp":" 947080166189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 9"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080166423","data":{"timestamp":" 947080166423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" baba_mjoma-kinyozi-mwanafunzi-baba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 10"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080166723","data":{"timestamp":" 947080166723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080166998","data":{"timestamp":" 947080166998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080167289","data":{"timestamp":" 947080167288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 3"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080167773","data":{"timestamp":" 947080167773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 4"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080168105","data":{"timestamp":" 947080168105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 5"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080168415","data":{"timestamp":" 947080168415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 6"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080168722","data":{"timestamp":" 947080168722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 7"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080172306","data":{"timestamp":" 947080172306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 8"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080173946","data":{"timestamp":" 947080173946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" wakulima_wakulima-babu-kinyozi-baba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 9"," expectedAnswer":" wakulima"," userResponse":" wakulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080174361","data":{"timestamp":" 947080174360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" watoto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080177988","data":{"timestamp":" 947080177988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" people_1"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:people","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080180006","data":{"timestamp":" 947080180005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" 61ffa9e2-bf30-429e-a714-7c7d54af76f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_people"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mwanafunzi_watoto-mwalimu-kaka-mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947080194578","data":{"timestamp":" 947080194578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_160702"," gameId":" a02d0c3c-2ce0-4c73-901a-4caaa6b19b37"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}